<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="email">"dario@innocliq.de"</string>
  <string name="link_playstore">"http://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.innocliq.instaq"</string>
  <string name="error_button_back">"Ir a la página principal"</string>
  <string name="error_button_try_again">"Inténtalo de nuevo"</string>
  <string name="error_desc2">"Algo salió mal y no podemos atender su solicitud"</string>
  <string name="error_desc">"Algo salió mal :("</string>
  <string name="error_headline">"Ooops ..."</string>
  <string name="exit_warning">"Tap again to exit"</string>
  <string name="rate_yes">"Califica ahora"</string>
  <string name="rate_no">"Nunca"</string>
  <string name="rate_later">"Más tarde"</string>
  <string name="rate_desc">"Si te gusta usar esta aplicación, ¿te importaría tomarte un momento para calificarla? ¡Gracias por tu apoyo! You will receive 3 photo uploads! :)"</string>
  <string name="rate_stars">"☆ ☆ ☆ ☆ ☆"</string>
  <string name="rate_headline">"Califica"</string>
  <string name="share">"Oye, me gustaría recomendarte esta aplicación: ayuda a encontrar los hashtags de Instagram más relevantes para fotos. Deja que también te ayude :)"</string>
  <string name="myhashtags_other">"Hashtags de fotos"</string>
  <string name="myhashtags_your">"Agregado por ti mismo"</string>
  <string name="myhashtags_intro">"Guarde sus hashtags favoritos aquí. Puedes acceder a ellos directamente desde la selección de fotos"</string>
  <string name="progressbar_freemode_time">"En%% s recibe 1 carga sin censura"</string>
  <string name="progressbar_results_freemode2">"Compra subidas de fotos para desbloquear hashtags"</string>
  <string name="progressbar_results_freemode1">"Límite libre alcanzado: los mejores hashtags están ocultos"</string>
  <string name="progressbar_confirm_freemode2">"Los mejores hashtags están ocultos ahora :("</string>
  <string name="progressbar_confirm_freemode1">"Límite libre alcanzado:"</string>
  <string name="progressbar_confirm_promode">"Quedan%% s fotos: disfruta de los mejores hashtags"</string>
  <string name="progressbar_home_freemode">"Usaste todas tus subidas de fotos gratis. Todavía puedes subir fotos pero algunos hashtags serán censurados"</string>
  <string name="progressbar_home_iapmode">"Usaste%% s de%% s cargas de fotos"</string>
  <string name="progressbar_home_startmode_is_using">"Has usado %1$s de %2$s subidas de fotos. Después de usarlas todas, obtienes 1 subida de fotos cada 24 horas gratis"</string>
  <string name="progressbar_home_startmode_not_used">"Obtén %1$s subidas de fotos gratis"</string>
  <string name="toast_imagepicker_failed">"Error al seleccionar fotos. Compruebe el permiso de lectura"</string>
  <string name="toast_create_customer_at_upload_failed">"¡Solicitud fallida! Conexión perdida: \'("</string>
  <string name="toast_create_customer_failed">"Estás desconectado. Conéctate a Internet :)"</string>
  <string name="toast_upload_failed">"¡Error de subida! Conexión perdida :\'("</string>
  <string name="toast_delete_failed">"Error al eliminar: \'("</string>
  <string name="toast_delete_successful">"Eliminación exitosa :)"</string>
  <string name="toast_no_hashtags_selected">"Seleccione primero los hashtags :)"</string>
  <string name="toast_hashtags_hidden">"El hashtag está oculto debido al Modo Libre: \'("</string>
  <string name="settings_rate_subline">"¡Gracias por su apoyo! :)"</string>
  <string name="settings_rate">"Calificar en Play Store"</string>
  <string name="settings_share_subline">"Cuéntales a tus amigos sobre esto"</string>
  <string name="settings_share">"¡Difunde un poco de amor!"</string>
  <string name="settings_terms">"Términos y Condiciones"</string>
  <string name="settings_legal">"Privacidad y Términos Legales"</string>
  <string name="settings_about">"Acerca de mí"</string>
  <string name="faq_buy_cancel">"Cancel"</string>
  <string name="faq_buy_cta">"Buy now for 1 €"</string>
  <string name="faq_buy_desc">"You\'re just one click away from unlocking \"%1$s\" and all other Tips &amp; Tricks sections :)"</string>
  <string name="faq_buy_headline">"Unlock all Tips &amp; Tricks"</string>
  <string name="faq_outro">"Mejorar esta página: ¿Alguna idea? ¿Quiere darnos su opinión o consejo? Háganoslo saber a través del formulario de comentarios"</string>
  <string name="iap_restored_successful_btn">"Perfecto"</string>
  <string name="iap_restored_successful_msg">"El producto \'%% s\' ha sido restaurado :)"</string>
  <string name="iap_restored_successful_title">"Restaurado"</string>
  <string name="iap_purchase_successful_btn">"Genial"</string>
  <string name="iap_purchase_successful_msg">"Has comprado con éxito%% s :)"</string>
  <string name="iap_purchase_successful_title">"Felicitaciones"</string>
  <string name="iap_purchase_failed">"La compra fue cancelada"</string>
  <string name="store_buy_failed">"Lamentablemente, su cuenta parece no ser elegible para realizar pagos :("</string>
  <string name="store_save">"Guardar"</string>
  <string name="store_restore">"Restaurar pagos"</string>
  <string name="store_price_per_photo">"equals %1$s per photo"</string>
  <string name="store_outro_apple">"Apple"</string>
  <string name="store_outro_google">"Google"</string>
  <string name="store_outro">"Tenga en cuenta que %1$s obtiene un 30%% por cada transacción que realice"</string>
  <string name="store_headline_abo">"Suscripciones"</string>
  <string name="store_headline_once">"Paquetes únicos"</string>
  <string name="store_intro">"Compre subidas de fotos para obtener más resultados de hashtags sin censura. Estas ventas no me traerán ningún beneficio, pero me ayudarán a cubrir los costes de esta aplicación"</string>
  <string name="menu_feedback">"Comentarios"</string>
  <string name="menu_settings">"Más"</string>
  <string name="menu_new">"new"</string>
  <string name="menu_faq">"Consejos y Trucos"</string>
  <string name="menu_store">"Tienda"</string>
  <string name="menu_myhashtags">"Mis hashtags"</string>
  <string name="menu_home">"Inicio"</string>
  <string name="about_infos_user_id">"ID de Usuario"</string>
  <string name="about_infos_be_version">"Versión de Backend"</string>
  <string name="about_infos_app_version">"Versión de la Aplicación"</string>
  <string name="about_infos_contact">"Soporte"</string>
  <string name="about_headline_infos">"Información"</string>
  <string name="about_made_in_hh_2">"en Hamburgo"</string>
  <string name="about_made_in_hh_1">"Hecho con amor"</string>
  <string name="about_support_others">"All other People for Translations and Tips &amp; Tricks"</string>
  <string name="about_support_4">"Nazar Nastin (Diseño)"</string>
  <string name="about_support_2">"Andreas Sefzig (Comentarios)"</string>
  <string name="about_support_1">"Tim Wiesenmüller (Comentarios)"</string>
  <string name="about_headline_support">"Compatible con"</string>
  <string name="about_credits_1">"Dario D. Müller desde Hamburg, Alemania"</string>
  <string name="about_headline_credits">"Desarrollado por"</string>
  <string name="about_desc_3">"¡Permítanos mejorar esta aplicación juntos! Por favor contribuya dándome sus comentarios sobre hashtags o dígame qué le gusta o qué no le gusta"</string>
  <string name="about_desc_2">"Creo que podemos mejorar la forma de encontrar los hashtags más relevantes. Me gustaría proporcionar una aplicación para ayudar a todos a encontrar los hashtags más relevantes. Para conseguirlo, el software detrás de esta aplicación recopila y analiza miles de fotos en Instagram "</string>
  <string name="about_desc_1">"Gracias por usar esta Aplicación :)"</string>
  <string name="about_title">"Acerca de mí"</string>
  <string name="settings_footer_title_fallback">"Compartir"</string>
  <string name="settings_footer_title">"Síguenos"</string>
  <string name="feedback_modal_button">"OK"</string>
  <string name="feedback_successful_desc">"Su comentario ha sido enviado :)"</string>
  <string name="feedback_successful_headline">"¡Gracias!"</string>
  <string name="feedback_send">"Enviar comentarios"</string>
  <string name="feedback_message">"Su mensaje"</string>
  <string name="feedback_email">"Su correo electrónico (opcional)"</string>
  <string name="feedback_intro">"Espero que te guste la aplicación. ¡Para mejorarla, me encantaría saber más sobre ti! Si tienes algún comentario, inquietud o idea, escríbenos o envíame un correo electrónico a: dario@innocliq.de "</string>
  <string name="feedback_title">"Mejora esta aplicación"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact22">"El 30%% de los usuarios compraron un producto que descubrieron en Instagram"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact21">"400 millones de usuarios miran historias de Instagram a diario"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact20">"Los hashtags con 21-24 caracteres funcionan mejor que los hashtags más cortos porque son más específicos"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact19">"El 60%% de las principales marcas utilizan el mismo filtro para cada publicación"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact18">"Las fotos que tienen el azul como color dominante obtienen un 24%% más de me gusta que las imágenes que tienen rojo como color dominante"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact17">"Las fotos con más espacio de fondo (negativo o espacio en blanco) obtienen un 29%% más de me gusta"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact16">"Las fotos con un solo tono dominante tienen los mejores resultados"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact15">"Las publicaciones que contienen o presentan contenido generado por el usuario tienen una tasa de conversión de un 4.5%% mayor que las publicaciones que no son UGC"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact14">"Las marcas publican un promedio de 27.9x por mes, lo que significa que casi publican todos los días"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact13">"Los cinco hashtags de Instagram más utilizados son #love, #instagood, #fashion, #photooftheday y #style"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact12">"1.100 millones de personas usan Instagram, pero solo 500 millones lo usan todos los días"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact11">"Las publicaciones con una ubicación reciben un 79%% más de interacción"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact10">"Las publicaciones que incluyen etiquetar otro identificador obtienen un 56%% más de interacción"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact9">"El Miércoles a las 5 pm es el mejor momento para publicar una foto"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact8">"A medida que subes hashtag hasta llegar a los 11 aumenta su visibilidad"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact7">"Los videos obtienen 2 veces más interacción que las fotos"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact6">"El 17%% de los adolescentes dice que Instagram es la red social más importante"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact5">"38%% de las mujeres y 26%% de los usuarios de internet hombres usan Instagram"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact4">"El 68%% de los usuarios de Instagram son Mujeres"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact3">"Las publicaciones con al menos un hashtag alcanzan un promedio de 12.6%% más de interacción"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact2">"32%% de todos los usuarios de Internet están en Instagram"</string>
  <string name="diduknow_fact1">"Alrededor de 95 millones de fotos se suben a Instagram todos los días"</string>
  <string name="loading_status2">"Analizando"</string>
  <string name="loading_status1">"Subiendo"</string>
  <string name="loading_desc">"¿Sabías que?"</string>
  <string name="loading_headline">"Construyendo #hashtags"</string>
  <string name="leave_feedback_send_feedback_copy">"Enviar comentarios"</string>
  <string name="leave_feedback_send_feedback">"Enviar y transferirlos a Instagram"</string>
  <string name="leave_feedback_comments">"¿Cómo puedo mejorarlo?"</string>
  <string name="leave_feedback_missing_hashtags">"¿Faltan hashtags?"</string>
  <string name="leave_feedback_bad_hashtags_desc">"Hashtags que están fuera de contexto …"</string>
  <string name="leave_feedback_bad_hashtags_title">"¿Hashtags inapropiados?"</string>
  <string name="leave_feedback_good_hashtags_desc">"Hashtags que más me gustan …"</string>
  <string name="leave_feedback_good_hashtags_title">"¿Hashtags particularmente coincidentes?"</string>
  <string name="leave_feedback_rating_desc">"Califica los resultados"</string>
  <string name="leave_feedback_rating_title">"¿Te gustaron los hashtags?"</string>
  <string name="emoji_bad">"Malo"</string>
  <string name="emoji_satisfied">"Satisfecho"</string>
  <string name="emoji_great">"Genial"</string>
  <string name="leave_feedback_headline">"Calificar hashtags"</string>
  <string name="leave_feedback_skip">"Saltar"</string>
  <string name="results_ok_to_leave_feedback">"Give Feedback"</string>
  <string name="copy_failed">"Copia fallida"</string>
  <string name="copy_please_give_feedback">"Califique los resultados del hashtag …"</string>
  <string name="copy_successful">"Copiado al portapapeles"</string>
  <string name="results_made_with_app">"made with #hashtagBuddyApp"</string>
  <string name="results_copy_to_instagram">"Transferir a Instagram"</string>
  <string name="results_copy_selected">"Copiar seleccionado"</string>
  <string name="results_copy_top">"Copia los 20 principales"</string>
  <string name="results_hashtags_add">"Agregar"</string>
  <string name="results_hashtags_input">"Agregue sus propios #hashtags"</string>
  <string name="results_recommented_amount">"Mejor elegir al menos"</string>
  <string name="results_no_hashtags_selected">"Seleccione hashtags de abajo …"</string>
  <string name="results_deselect_all">"Ningún"</string>
  <string name="results_select_all">"Todo"</string>
  <string name="results_category_location_based_hashtags">"Basado en la ubicación"</string>
  <string name="results_category_favorites">"Mis hashtags"</string>
  <string name="results_category_upcoming_has">"Tendencias hashtags"</string>
  <string name="results_category_generic_hashtags">"Hashtags Genéricos"</string>
  <string name="results_category_niche_hashtags">"Hashtags de Nicho"</string>
  <string name="results_category_user_hashtags">"Mis hashtags seleccionados"</string>
  <string name="results_headline">"Hashtags"</string>
  <string name="selection_popup_button_deny">"Elige otra"</string>
  <string name="selection_popup_button_ok">"Que comience la magia"</string>
  <string name="selection_popup_title">"Al subir una foto, se descubrirán los hashtags más relevantes de Instagram"</string>
  <string name="history_photo_defect2">"Intenta volver a re-subirla"</string>
  <string name="history_photo_defect1">"Se produjo un error:"</string>
  <string name="history_no_content">"Todavía no has subido ninguna foto"</string>
  <string name="history_title">"Historial"</string>
  <string name="home_upload">"Elige una foto"</string>
  <string name="home_desc_3">"Sube una foto para obtener los hashtags adecuados de Instagram"</string>
  <string name="home_desc_2">"#hashtags para tus fotos"</string>
  <string name="home_desc_1">"Descubre el mejor Instagram"</string>
  <string name="_app_name_1k3Sbz">"Hashtag Buddy"</string>
  <string name="app_name">"Hashtag Buddy"</string>
  <string name="title_activity_kimera">"Hashtag Buddy"</string>
  <string name="offer">"You received a gift! Unlock all Tips &amp; Tricks and get x photo uploads now for just x € - How does that sound?"</string>
  <string name="offer_headline">"Special offer"</string>
  <string name="faq_11_desc">"As your profile grows, you will sooner or later receive requests from companies. This is about you recommending products and services to your community. Companies hope for attention and additional sales, just like with traditional advertising. With smaller profiles, it is usually a matter of providing you with a product or service free of charge and then sharing it with your community. If your profile is slightly larger or has other unique selling points that are particularly interesting for the brand, a remuneration will also be agreed. If you advertise a brand, make sure that it matches the characteristics of your profile. When it comes to healthy eating, it would be funny and ironical when you suddenly advertise a fast food chain. Choose your partners according to what fits your content and what is interesting for your community. Even if the offers are tempting at the beginning, think about what will help you in the long run to support your credibility.\n\nAlso outside of advertising it makes sense to cooperate with other profiles of your target group through shout-outs. This means that you can recommend other Instagram profiles to your community via posts and stories, or someone can recommend you. There are also theme profiles that sell shoutouts although they don\'t often have as much reach as you might hope. What works better is to interact with similar profiles and give each other reciprocative shout-outs. But you can also simply recommend personal profiles that you like anyway. Maybe the person is happy about it and shares it in their story, or their followers find you even more likeable and recommend you to others.\n\nIf you do advertising, you should mark it as such. Even if the products might be used anyway, it is important that your followers can classify whether you bought the product yourself or whether it was sent to you free of charge. In addition, you avoid the danger of a warning."</string>
  <string name="faq_11_headline">"Cooperation and Authenticity"</string>
  <string name="faq_10_desc">"Instagram gives you the ability to go live and communicate with your community in real-time. You can also add viewers to your live video and answer questions, for example. This feature is also great for conducting interviews where questions from viewers can be answered as well. This format builds very high credibility to your followers because nothing can be cut or taken back. In addition, live streams that are currently running will be highlighted in the story for your followers, and some push notifications will be sent that you are live. At the end of your live session, you have the option to save the recording with your stories so that it can be retrieved for another 24 hours.\n\nWith InstaTV you have the possibility to upload longer videos. InstaTV is similar to Youtube but in portrait format. For example, if you want to record longer tutorials, InstaTV is a good choice. As usual, you have the possibility to post a preview in your profile so that your community can watch the beginning of the video and complete watching it on InstaTV. You have the opportunity to comment and interact here as well."</string>
  <string name="faq_10_headline">"Live &amp; InstaTV"</string>
  <string name="faq_9_desc">"Hashtags are used to bundle posts on different topics so that people can easily find such things as recipes, yoga exercises, and sports among other topics. Use hashtags both in your posts and stories. Make sure that you only choose hashtags that are relevant to your topic. By varying the selection of hashtags, you can address different aspects of your content and reach different audiences. Also, pay attention to the language of your hashtags. If you post in German, it makes sense to use only German hashtags. If you use Instagram to display hashtags in your search, you will see popular posts and you can display them chronologically. If you use very large hashtags with millions of posts, it is less likely that you will be displayed among the popular posts. See that you combine large and small hashtags. Avoid hashtags that are too general and are used in combination with any kind of photo, for example, #travel for travel photos, instead use #sheisnotlost or similar.\n\nMany post the hashtags, not in the caption, but in the first comment to make it look more professional. But it\'s not quite clear whether Instagram evaluates this with a smaller range. Alternatively, you can post line spacing by dots and thus post the hashtags further down in your caption. To find the best and most appropriate hashtags, use the hashtag generator function of this app. It quickly happens that you use the same hashtags over and over again. So that you always expand your community and address new followers, alternate your hashtags regularly and add hashtags that fit the photo or mood."</string>
  <string name="faq_9_headline">"Hashtags"</string>
  <string name="faq_8_desc">"Your followers and their habits determine the best time to post. Many browse through Instagram on their way to work or while relaxing on the sofa in the evenings. The exact time will vary depending on which audience you\'re targeting. Your followers may also have their own habits. If you are unsure, go to the exchange and ask. Also, consider the country that your followers come from. If you write in English, your community is often more scattered and the right time to post loses importance. A good orientation is your statistics on the Instagram App. Here you can find out where most of your followers come from, but also when most of them are online. Basically, the more often you post, the more attention you get, but quality goes before quantity. Many influencers follow the strategy quite successfully: One post per day.\n\nInstagram Stories are a bit different, and here it makes sense to record something several times a day. Thus your story appears again and again at the beginning of the list. I recommend that you always have about 5 stories online, posted periodically and one at time. If you are unsure how often you should post something, check other profiles on your topic, how often they post and how high the interactions are. Basically, it is better to watch short videos on a regular basis. You can also post automatically with platforms such as later.com, which means you can prepare everything and your posts will then be posted automatically at the appropriate times. However, it is not clear whether the use of such platforms has a negative impact on Instagram algorithms. It is important that you are still active and interact as soon as the post is online."</string>
  <string name="faq_8_headline">"What Time &amp; Frequency"</string>
  <string name="faq_7_desc">"Don\'t see Instagram as an advertising platform to share information, but as a way to communicate with others and share common interests. If you simply post a picture of your food, it\'s uninteresting to many people. But if you post a recipe, or tips for a healthy diet, or perhaps your personal experiences on specific diets, you offer your followers added value and stand out from the crowd of other Instagram profiles. You can combine this with asking questions in the caption about how others eat or what experiences they have had on a specific subject. This will encourage your followers to interact with you and each other in your community. The more personal you are, the more personal your followers\' comments will be.\n\nInstagram is a social media platform that rewards interactions. It is especially important in the first hour after publication that you get likes and comments in your posts, as the algorithm of Instagram considers posts with a higher interaction rate to be more interesting and thus appear to more users. Answer comments below your posts as well - this is, of course, part of the excellent tone. If Instagram finds your post relevant, hashtags will help you to be found in the search and via subscribed hashtags. Don\'t just shout into the forest and wait for an echo, use the features Instagram has to offer: Find profiles that do something similar to what you’re doing and comment under their posts or reply to comments there. Create an exchange with the community to be sympathetic and accessible."</string>
  <string name="faq_7_headline">"Community &amp; Interactions"</string>
  <string name="faq_6_desc">"Maybe you\'ve heard this sentence before: A post must encourage you to visit your profile and the feed design must encourage you to subscribe to your profile. Have you ever seen posts that you really liked, but somehow the pictures didn\'t fit together properly? Create a recognition value in your photos: You can do this by special image editing, or by always shooting in the same light conditions. Many also use filters such as the VSCO app or image editing with Lightroom or Snapseed as a recognition value. Please do not use the filters offered by Instagram, or at least dim them down a lot. It is also important that a thematic and graphical context is recognizable. If you want to check how your photos harmonize with each other, you can use apps like UNUM or Later.com and move your pictures back and forth. Please have a look at the why section again.\n\nInstagram Stories are short videos that are deleted after 24 hours. Many use the stories as a kind of \"Behind the Scenes\" where they report about their everyday life behind the scenes of the beautiful photos. The stories are considered more authentic by many and are now more popular than the posts themselves. To reach more followers here, you can link people, set hashtags and mark places. If someone is looking for a hashtag, your stories will also be displayed there. Other useful tools to increase the interaction with your community are regular surveys, the Q&amp;A Tool and many more. If you don\'t want your story to be deleted, you can mark it as a highlight. Highlights make sense, especially when highlighting topics of interest. You can create individual cover pictures so that it matches your feed better. For this, you can use the Canva tool, for example. I also recommend that you create an \"About me\" highlight in which you introduce yourself to the community and explain what they can expect on your profile. For 10,000 followers or more, you get the Swipe-Up function, which lets you integrate a link into your story that takes you away from Instagram. For paid ads, the Swipe-Up feature is always available."</string>
  <string name="faq_6_headline">"Stories"</string>
  <string name="faq_5_desc">"Your Instagram Bio is the only explanation that people see when they visit your profile, your figurehead. Due to the few available signs, the Bio is always a small test of how far you\'ve got in your positioning. Your bio must clearly bring out what you are all about. You can consider a list form, a sentence or a question that can help to arouse curiosity. Be creative and let others inspire you without copying. Your profile visitors should be able to get an immediate idea of what you are all about.\n\nThe space under your bio is the only space (apart from the Swipe Up function) for a clickable link that leads away from Instagram. Instagram wants to keep users on the platform for as long as possible. Place your most important link here, e.g. to your website. If you want to place more links, it makes sense to use providers for link lists such as linktr.ee. However, with every click, users will be redirected to the link and some people could get lost. So use the site only if it makes sense."</string>
  <string name="faq_5_headline">"Biography &amp; URL"</string>
  <string name="faq_4_desc">"How would you like to appear on Instagram? With your real name or a fantasy name? Of course, it\'s fun to be creative. If you present yourself as a theme profile, you can, of course, use a name that is interesting, creative and memorable. But be aware that your followers will always associate you with that name, which can make it difficult if you decide at some point to post content on a different topic. There is the possibility to change the name, but you should be aware that a name change is confusing for your followers and you will lose followers. If you already have a brand, it always makes sense to use the brand name on Instagram as well. Moving on to profile pictures,  a portrait photo turned out to be recommendable with personal profiles. Even if you don\'t want to post photos of yourself, because you might be dealing with photography or post quotes, it helps your followers to classify you and get to know you better. If you post for a brand, it may make sense to use a team photo of your company. If you\'d rather use the brand logo as a profile picture, it\'s always a good idea to introduce the team elsewhere so that the followers feel better taken along."</string>
  <string name="faq_4_headline">"Name &amp; Profile Picture"</string>
  <string name="faq_3_desc">"Instagram distinguishes between personal profiles and theme profiles. If your Instagram profile focuses on you, then it is considered a personal profile - even if you focus on a specific topic, e.g. by positioning yourself as an expert. The advantage of personal profiles is that followers can put themselves better in your position as a person and the feeling of friendship arises. Besides, a personal profile is less tied to the content. You may win followers because of a certain topic or problem, but they stay because of your personality and authenticity.\n\nA topic profile is really only about one topic, such as food or sports. Many brands tend to use a theme profile and then work with influencers with a personal profile to share their posts in their feed. Topic profiles are quicker and easier to classify. This makes it easier to find followers (with the same quality as the community) because profile visitors can see at a glance whether the topic interests them. The downside is that they also develop faster because of the missing personal or emotional relationship to your Instagram."</string>
  <string name="faq_3_headline">"Personal or thematic profile?"</string>
  <string name="faq_2_desc">"What is your goal on Instagram? Only if you know your purpose, can you determine the path to achieve it. Why is it important to you that others follow you at all? Is it about making the world a better place? Then go out with your mission, take others along with your content and make them understand why this is so important to you. If you’re passionate about a topic, share your passion and be emotional. If you love sharing with others, Instagram is made for you: Start communicating through your posts with questions and interact as much as you can with your followers. When it comes to getting products sent to you, give brands a reason to trust you and invest in you. But first of all, it is important that your followers trust you. Start by recommending the things you like and use anyway, like which products you have tried and haven\'t been convinced with at all. If you manage to win the trust of your followers, sooner or later, brands will follow suit.\n\nIf you already have your own company and want to inspire your followers for your brand and its products, then tell them why your products are good, but not as in classical advertising, but tell them stories about their creation. Also, talk about failures or challenges and how you learned to overcome them. People love to follow the development process. Many TV shows are based on this principle. First, determine your goal and the message behind it, so as to decide on a strategy to pursue and present your stories."</string>
  <string name="faq_2_headline">"Know your Why"</string>
  <string name="faq_1_desc">"Do you want many people to follow you on Instagram? Then give them a reason to follow you. To find out why people should follow you, first ask yourself: What problem can you solve? Maybe you know crazy recipes, have an exciting sense of humour to entertain people, are an absolute trendsetter and whose creations inspire others. Whatever reason it is, consider exactly what value you can create next to beautiful pictures and your personality to offer your followers an added value. You should also ask yourself what sets your profile apart from others who deal with the same subject: What makes you unique? What is your USP (Unique Selling Point)? Highlight it in your profile."</string>
  <string name="faq_1_headline">"Create added value"</string>
  <string name="faq_unlocked">"unlocked"</string>
  <string name="faq_locked">"locked"</string>
  <string name="faq_premium">"Premium"</string>
  <string name="store_buy_tips_tricks">"Acquire tips &amp; tricks"</string>
  <string name="store_buy_photo">"Acquire photo uploads"</string>
  <string name="feedback_via_email">"Oder sende mir eine E-Mail an:"</string>
  <string name="results_category_upcoming_hashtags">"Trending hashtags"</string>
  <string name="_tasso_si__uCsii">"tasso_si\'"</string>
  <string name="Toast_imagepicker_failed">"Toast_imagepicker_failed"</string>
</resources>
